<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nikita Voloboev</title>
    <link>https://learn-anything.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nikita Voloboev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Built with 💗 using [Hugo](https://gohugo.io) and [Minimal](https://github.com/calintat/minimal) theme</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://learn-anything.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://learn-anything.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn-anything.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>👋 I love making and sharing things I have built with the world.
🚙 Born in Moscow; currently based in Eindhoven, Netherlands.
🔭 I am creating an Open Source Website for learning any topic on Earth with Interactive Mind Maps.
🚀 With it, I want to accelerate the way in which people learn by providing the most efficient paths for learning anything.
🖋 I also love writing. You can read all that I have said on Medium or take a look at my constantly expanding personal wiki where I share everything I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://learn-anything.xyz/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn-anything.xyz/projects/</guid>
      <description>I am currently working and focusing my time on making and improving Learn Anything.
I am continuously learning, reading books and writing various tools and Alfred workflows for my own personal productivity.
My current and past projects include :
Learn Anything Learn Anything is an Open Source Website that searches user curated Mind Maps of links and resources to learn anything in the most efficient way.
I genuinely believe it can change the world for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://learn-anything.xyz/likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn-anything.xyz/likes/</guid>
      <description>Animals I have been vegeterian for over 4 years now and it has been one of the best decisions I have made thus far in my life.
I think everyone has a choice nowadays of what they can eat and animal suffering can be avoided.
Writing I try to share my knowledge and experiences by writing about it in my blog and I maintain my own written knowledge wiki in the spirit of continuous learning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>